A Guide to the Papers of Everett Parker Lesley, Jr.
Old Dominion University
- Series VI: Printed Materials
  - Sub-series B: Newspaper Articles
    - Article on Lesley, Action Magazine, Oct. 19, 1968 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Memorial, ODU Courier, Feb. 26, 1982 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Obituary, Virginian-Pilot, Feb. 15, 1982 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Sub-series C: Miscellaneous
    - "A Loan Exhibition of Antique Automatons" by Alfred Chapius, Nov. 3 - Dec. 5, 1950 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Reference materials in (French), dates unknown (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Reference materials in (German), dates unknown (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Review of "Renaissance Jewels and Jeweled Objects", 1968 (Box-folder 7:8)
- Series VII: Photo Slides
  - Sub-series A: Belgium
    - Antwerp, June 1969 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Sub-series B: England
    - Wooten Under Edge, Gloucestershire, Nov. 1969 (slides developed) (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Sub-series C: Israel
    - Akko, Aug. 9, 1967 (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Ashqelon, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:12)
    - Avdat, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:13)
    - Bar'am, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:14)
    - Beit Shean, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:15)
    - Beit She'arim, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:16)
    - Bethlehem, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:17)
    - Caesarea, Aug. 7, 1967 (Box-folder 7:18)
    - Cana, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:19)
    - Capernaum, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:20)
    - Galilee, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:21)
    - Hefa, Aug. 6-11, 1967 (Box-folder 7:22)
    - Jaffa, Aug. 2, 1967 (Box-folder 7:23)
    - Jerusalem, Aug. 16, 1967 (Box-folder 7:24)
    - Kiryat-Ono, Aug. 4, 1967 (Box-folder 7:25)
    - Lod, Aug. 5, 1967 (Box-folder 7:26)
    - Maghor, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:27)
    - Massada, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:28)
    - Megiddo, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:29)
    - Meiron, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:30)
    - Miscellaneous set 1, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:31)
    - Miscellaneous set 2, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:32)
    - Miscellaneous set 3, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:33)
    - Miscellaneous set 4, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:34)
    - Miscellaneous set 5, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:35)
    - Miscellaneous set 6, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:36)
    - Miscellaneous set 7, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:37)
    - Miscellaneous set 8, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:38)
    - Miscellaneous set 9, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:39)
    - Miscellaneous set 10, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:40)
    - Miscellaneous set 11, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:41)
    - Miscellaneous set 12, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:42)
    - Montfort, Aug. 10, 1967 (Box-folder 7:43)
    - Mt. of the Beatitudes, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:44)
    - Nazareth, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:45)
    - Ramla, Aug. 5, 1967 (Box-folder 7:46)
    - Safed, Aug. 14, 1967 (Box-folder 7:47)
    - Tabgha, Aug. 13, 1967 (Box-folder 7:48)
    - Tel-Aviv, Aug. 3, 1967 (Box-folder 7:49)
    - Tel-Qasile, Aug. 3, 1967 (Box-folder 7:50)
    - Wilderness of Zin, Aug. 1967 (Box-folder 7:51)
  - Sub-series D: Massachusetts, U.S.A.
    - Massachusetts, May 1969 (slides developed) (Box-folder 7:52)
  - Sub-series E: Turkey
    - Ephesus, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:53)
    - Miletus, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:54)
    - Miscellaneous set 1, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:55)
    - Miscellaneous set 2, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:56)
    - Miscellaneous set 3, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:57)
    - Miscellaneous set 4, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:58)
    - Miscellaneous set 5, July 1970 (Box-folder 7:59)
    - Miscellaneous set 6, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Miscellaneous set 7, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Miscellaneous set 8, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Miscellaneous set 9, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Miscellaneous set 10, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Miscellaneous set 11, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Miscellaneous set 12, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Miscellaneous set 13, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Priene, July 1970 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Sub-series F: Virginia, U.S.A.
    - Norfolk, date unknown (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Sub-series G: Miscellaneous
    - set 1, date unknown (Box-folder 8:11)
    - set 2, date unknown (Box-folder 8:12)
    - set 3, date unknown (Box-folder 8:13)
- Series VIII: Photographs
  - Sub-series A: California, U.S.A.
    - California, Oct. - Dec. 1979 (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Sub-series B: E. Parker Lesley, Jr.
    - E. Parker Lesley, Jr., 1914 - (1981?) (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Sub-series C: Lesley with others
    - 1914 - 1942 (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Sub-series D: Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous, 1907 - 1938 (Box-folder 8:17)
- Series IX: Miscellaneous
  - Catalog of Works by A. L. Pocock, date unknown (Box-folder 8:18)
  - "In Memory of Parker Lesley", Feb. 19, 1982 (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Mrs. E. P. Lesley, Sr.'s recollection of Parker Lesley, Jr., Apr. 11, 1949 - ? (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Miscellaneous paper, Sept. 3, 1978 (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Picture, artist unknown, (1959? - 1962?) (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Postcards, date unknown (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Gertrude Stein lecture, Apr. 2, 1980 - Feb. 25, 1981 (Box-folder 8:24)
- Series X: Negatives
  - Negatives (Box-folder 9:1)
- Series XI: Artifacts
  - "General Tours" button (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Russian button (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Russian coins (Box-folder 9:4)